In this class, we'll build an app called Pitch Perfect,
which lets you record your voice and play it back with changes to pitch.
To do this, we'll explore and get comfortable with
Xcode, Apple's development environment.
You can use Xcode to create apps for any of
Apple's platforms from the Watch to Apple TV to iOS,
and even the Mac.
This lesson, Introduction and Xcode,
is about getting comfortable with Xcode.
In Audio Layouts and Buttons,
we'll set up the initial screen of the app for the user to record their own voice.
We'll learn how to lay out the user interface,
how to connect UI elements such as our buttons to code.
In ViewController and Multiple Views,
we're going to step it up a notch by adding a second screen
to the app where the user can apply audio effects.
Next, in Delegation and Recording,
we'll explore how to pass the recorded audio from the first screen to the second.
Then in Playback and Audio Effects,
we'll add the functionality for adding various alterations to the pitch.
As you progress through course,
you'll be practicing fundamental iOS concepts that you can
apply for any app that you build. Let's get started.