Hey everyone, it's me Jared.
And I'd like to show you the App we're going to
create in this course called Pitch Perfect.
Pitch Perfect allows you to record your voice and
play it back with various sound effects,
including changes to speed,
pitch and even reverb an echo.
I'm running it here in the iOS simulator so that I can show you.
The first screen simply prompts you to record your voice.
Here at Udacity we believe that asking questions is one of the best ways to learn.
Judge a man by his questions rather than by his answers.
Now, you can see that Pitch Perfect has moved this to the Playback View,
we can choose to playback my voice using a variety of different sound effects.
Let's try listening to my voice played back really fast.
"Judge a man by his questions rather than by his answers."
Or we can playback my voice at a really low pitch and I'll sound like Darth Vader.
This app is a lot of fun to play with,
but more importantly as you build this app you'll learn
key iOS development concepts along the way.