Before we move into writing the code for Pitch Perfect,
I want to cover a software design principle that you will
find very useful in every iOS app that you write.
Let me introduce the Model View Controller pattern called MVC for short.
MVC helps us to organize our code by separating
different parts of the application logic into distinct files.
You can think of any app as having three parts,
the view, which presents graphics, text,
and interactive elements to the user, the model,
which stores the apps data,
and the controller which connects the view and the model.
Now let's look at what this means for us.
You've seen Pitch Perfect's user interface.
It has two screens with buttons the user can tap. That's the view.
The model will hold the audio file that is produced when the user records their voice.
And finally, there's the logic for playing the audio with effects.
This connecting code lives in the controller.
You might be tempted to have the view and model talk directly to each other,
but to keep our code really clean the view and
model should know as little about each other as possible.
They'll tell the controller what they need,
and the controller will relay messages between them.
For example, when the user presses a button,
the view passes the user's intent along to the controller for processing.
And the controller, in turn,
will talk to the model, if needed.
Similarly, when the model changes,
it notifies the controller,
which can then update the view, if needed.
Having a division of responsibility or separation of concerns between
the code that handles different kinds of tasks makes it much easier to write,
maintain, and reuse your code.
Students have found it really handy to have this pattern in the back of
their minds as they start building Pitch Perfect where you'll get to see the model,
view, and controller and how they work together. So let's get to it.